The weapons are flowing south.
The Contras are pushing back.
That's how you're funding this?
If we win this war.
we can change the course of history.
They charged you with a 187 PC.
Murder one.
Alton.
You wait till I'm in
here to be a fucking dad?
- Stop. Stop!
- Don't you fucking come back here!
- Wait!
- Stay the fuck away from me!
Franklin. Don't hurt him.
This is about getting my nephew
out of that prison.
So. if there is anything
that you can do. do it.
I don't think our Mr. Reed Thompson's
just some drug dealer.
I think he works for the government.
And now. well. I think we work for him.
DEA! Hands up!
Hands up. hands up.
We've been instructed to shut down
every facet of this
operation and walk away.
Cut Lucia and Gustavo loose.
What agency would
want to shut down a DEA operation?
Give me just long enough
for us to give the Nicaraguan people
their democracy back. and I promise you
that I will hand over
every distributor. every dealer
and every supplier that we work with
along the way.
If you falling for Claudia.
that's bad for business.
That's a problem.
I didn't invent this rock.
But I'm-a blow it up.
Mr. Wright.
- Officer Wright.
- How can I help you. Officer?
Stay the fuck away from me and mine.
That all?
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪ Snowfall 3x01 ♪
Protect and Swerve
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
It's all there.
Come on. now. You know how this works.
Come on. just give me the rock.
- Bitch. this only nine.
- Nuh-uh. that's ten.
- You saying I can't count?
- Just count it again.
- Hey. get out of here.
- Give me the rock. and I'll leave.
- Hey.
- Just come on.
- It's just one. one fucking dollar.
- Hey!
Hey. walk away.
Fuck this. You out of your goddamn mind?
Hey!
Whoa!
12 units. all two-bedroom. one-bath.
nine of them currently occupied.
All with water damage and shoddy wiring.
Any idea when the heat last worked?
I am pretty sure it does.
And I'm sure the inspections
will reveal good bones.
And the Summer Games has
this whole area on the rise.
We have a lender we like if you
decide you want to move forward.
We make an offer. it'll be cash.
I'd like a minute with my
partner. if you don't mind.
I'll be right outside if
you need anything at all.
Man sell any harder.
he's gonna pull a muscle.
You know. price per square
foot still seems high.
Needs a lot more work than we thought.
and not just new carpet and paint.
Mm. But long term?
This is the place.
Hey. Louie!
Come on. now!
Shit.
Getting dressed all the goddamn time.
Yeah. boy. you look good.
Hey. come on.
- Hmm?
- You ready?
Yeah. I'm waiting on you.
What you mean. waiting
on me? You made me late
- to my own goddamn opening.
- Hey.
Take a breath.
Come on.
It's gonna be perfect.
I'm so proud of you.
Mm-hmm. Mm.
I'm the luckiest motherfucker in the world.
It's just in front of 5 o' clock
at AM stereo KDAY Santa Monica and...
You ain't going too short. right?
I got you. baby.
Hey. Fatback. he going too short?
Oh. shit!
What?
What? Oh. come on.
Leon told me to dress nice.
Shit. Nice according to who.
the Solid Gold dancers?
Hey. you good. Rob. Don't listen to him.
- Hey. we cool?
- We good. man.
- Hey. you got a minute?
- Come on. little nigga.
- Rock sell over there.
- Man. I ain't want no rock.
I'm trying to get on. Heard
you was the man to see.
- Hey. come back later.
- Like. when?
Like when you get some hair
on your little balls. Watch out. yo.
Hey. man. come on.
man. give me a chance.
All right. I'm ready. Man.
I'll sell that shit like
- you ain't never seen.
- Get your bitch ass out of here. man.
- We said no.
- Leon. man. come on.
Ain't you got to be in school
or something like that?
I have another question for you. Reed.
_
I love Los Angeles.
Go every few months.
I stay at the Chateau.
eat at Mr. Chow.
Party...
well. everywhere.
This time.
- we went to the Roxy. you know it?
- Oh. yeah.
- Yeah. on Sunset.
- On Sunset. right.
I'm there. when I see
Burt "Rentals" come in.
Oh. come on. Burt Rentals.
Burt Rentals! I can't believe it.
I want to say hello to him.
but he is on his way upstairs
to a private club.
I was so angry.
The shame of being nothing.
- Okay.
- Fuck that place!
I never go back there!
I want to start my fucking
private club next door!
And I want you to be my partner.
Sorry. what?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What. what?
Right now. we are
connected in business only.
This is something we can
do that will entwine us.
ensure we are both in
the circle together.
the true fucking partners.
- Yeah. um. yeah. That's...
- Yeah.
You know. obviously. I'd love
to be in the circle with you.
You know that. I just... I don't
know anything about nightclubs.
You know the city.
And between us.
we have more money than Dios.
_
Unless you know of a reason why
you don't want to be my partner.
Listen. um...
... before we agree to this.
I-I think there's something
that you probably need to know.
It's a little tricky. but. um...
Okay. The DEA raids on your facility.
it was on the news. but that's not how I...
... I-I first heard about it.
See. I first heard about it from Lorena.
because she used to be DEA.
What was it that turned you?
Reed. here.
he convinced me that I was
fighting an unwinnable war.
So...
Thanks.
Thanks for your honesty.
It means everything.
So. let me know when
you've found our space.
To Rigo and Reed's.
That sounds good.
That sounds good. See you.
Hasta luego.
"To Rigo and Reed's".
Oh. come on.
- You good?
- Uh-huh.
♪ Five minutes of funk... ♪
All I'm saying.
you should've asked us first.
Jammin' Jeromes is the
best shit out. Ain't nothing better.
What about. like. Saints' Sexy Sounds?
Broken Boxes and Bullshit.
Leather and Loud Shit.
Hunky Unkie's Sultry Sounds.
Y'all niggas funny. I'm gonna
get my pistol. though. for you.
Y'all fucking... fucking up in my shit.
I have to say. I had my
doubts. but I was wrong.
This is wonderful. Jerome.
Mom and Dad would be so proud.
Thank you so much. Cissy.
Thank you for coming by. too. Alton.
Black-owned business
in a black neighborhood.
Congratulations. my brother.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
You know. this is just the start. too.
- This is just the start?
- Going nationwide next year.
- Ooh.
- Be bigger than that... RadioShack?
Oh. no. Make sure this one work first.
Was hoping I'd see you here.
Eva and Shon-Shon.
How y'all doing? Good?
- Not as good as y'all.
- Better if somebody'd
- offer us a fucking drink.
- Hey.
This is my best friend.
Leon. You met him?
Hey. Well. the bar
this way. So. let's go.
- Grab me something. all right?
- Yeah.
Damn. Look at you. You look great.
I feel great.
Got into Spelman.
Wow. That's... that's amazing.
Congratulations.
So. uh. guess that
means you leaving us now?
- Not till next month.
- Okay.
- Classes don't start till September. but...
- Mm-hmm.
I want to get settled. find a job.
A job? Nah. you got to
be on them books 24/7.
Here. Yep.
- Franklin. no.
- Been meaning to give you
a graduation gift anyway.
So you can focus on school.
♪ Your master rapper.
but when I'm on the Mic... ♪
Come on. it's the least I can do.
Hey. picture time!
Family. I need you outside.
If you ain't my goddamn family.
stay out my fucking frame.
Come on.
- Okay. come on.
- Come on.
All right. everybody outside. Come on.
He ain't took a picture in 15 years.
Well. hey. uh. don't worry about that.
You know how to use it. though?
Just tell us where
you want us to go. Jerome.
Hey y'all. come on. let's
take this picture so we can...
Oh. no. you go ahead. It's all right.
- Come on. man. get in here.
- Hey. where Opie at?
Bring old man Peaches up in here.
Come on in. Hey. Opie!
There it is.
- You okay to start unloading?
- Yeah.
We can't ignore this.
If the Medellín Cartel
has a source inside the DEA.
- we have to alert them.
- I hear you. but listen.
You start rattling those cages now.
and then Rigo's gonna know
that you're still in contact
with the DEA; then we're all at risk.
Teddy? These are federal
agents. They're good people.
I'm not gonna let this
go. and neither should you.
Okay. so let me take care of it.
I can have word trickle
down some other way.
some way that doesn't lead back to us.
- Help! Teddy! Ted...
- Matt?
Matt? Matt?
Whoa. What's wrong?
You okay? Whoa. whoa.
- Okay. okay. okay. Whoa. whoa. What's...
- Fuck.
- What hurts?
- My. um...
Did you have any numbness
in your hands today?
Do you have any nausea?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? He's having a heart attack.
Oh. come on. I'm only 13 minutes late.
Hey.
It's not my fault.
- Eva didn't want to leave.
- Listen. it's okay.
I don't want to spend our
last month together fighting.
All right?
Besides. it's not like I can come down
and check on you every night at school.
Here. sit with me a minute.
What's all this?
Ah. it's bills. taxes.
Life.
You have fun?
- It was okay.
- Just you and Eva?
- And Shon-Shon.
Shon-Shon. she the one who came in
- with the hickey on her neck?
- Dad.
- What?
- Come on.
What'd y'all do?
- We went ice fishing.
- Ice fishing. huh?
Did you catch anything?
Yeah.
One of them big ones.
You know. with the long. pointy nose.
- Ooh. a marlin.
- A marlin.
Yeah. But. uh. Eva slipped.
dropped the rod. and it got away.
That's too bad.
Oh. man.
So. uh...
Word is Franklin's uncle
has a new speaker joint
over off Western.
Hear anything about that?
Wow.
Mel. Mel.
What I said earlier is true.
I don't want to fight.
You've worked so hard.
You've done everything I asked.
I just want you to be smart.
Anything else?
I love you.
Man. I been wanting to fuck her.
Nah. man. that bitch got
summer teeth. you know?
Sum... ?
You know. some are here. some are there.
Her teeth are kind of fucked up.
Hey. I got to piss.
Some bushes over there. bro.
Look. I ain't pissing in no bushes.
- Then hold it. nigga.
- I ain't good to hold it.
That shit causes bacteria.
give you a bladder infection.
How the fuck you know that. nigga?
'Cause my mama a nurse's aide.
Yeah. Shit. hey. your mama can nurse me.
Man. hey. we've been long enough.
- Let's roll.
- Yeah. Yeah. you're right.
- There it is!
- Yeah. ice cream.
- All right. You all right there?
- Yeah. we good. man.
See that shit?
Hell yeah. Hell yeah.
Ah. shit.
Hey. what-what the fuck you two doing?
That the re-up truck. nigga.
Means it's loaded with cash and rock.
Also mean them boys strapped.
And Manboy told us scope out
the projects. not rob no truck.
We only scoping the niggas out
so we can rob these motherfuckers.
Once we get the shit. you just
make sure you're ready. a'ight?
Nigga. I ain't no getaway driver.
Hey!
Shit.
Oh. shit!
Come on.
Oh. shit.
Motherfucker!
- Levon and Dejon?
- They brothers.
Used to stay off Hoover.
Word is they with Manboy.
Who the fuck is Manboy?
Drew Miller. We all
went to Foshay together.
before his family moved Eastside.
- Fuck kind of name is Manboy?
- Who gives a shit?
Why he all up in our business?
Look. word is they cook and
sell their own shit for a while.
Maybe looking to expand.
But we got to answer this shit. Saint.
I want to know everything:
where they stay at.
where they sell. where they cook
and who the fuck put them on our truck.
Hold up.
Are you saying them boys is dead?
Yeah. I told them niggas that shit was
seven kinds of stupid.
but they wouldn't hear me.
They just ran up on them
niggas like they was the A-Team.
You dumb motherfuckers.
I told y'all who them
projects belong to.
Was you even listening to my story?
- You should've stopped them.
- I fucking tried!
- And a fine fucking job you did!
- Hey. chill!
You know how them niggas was.
You couldn't tell them shit.
This ain't on Tyrell.
I didn't teach y'all
how to cook up this rock
so you could get us all killed.
You best figure out
how to handle this shit.
'Cause Saint and 'em. they don't play.
Hey. look. first.
I need you to tell me
everything you know about Saint.
your boy Leon.
and everybody else in their crew.
- Okay? Okay?
- Okay. Okay.
You're late.
Just thought you ain't
never been late before.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah. I just hit a little snag.
It's nothing you need to worry about.
but. uh. I am gonna
need a little more time
to get you the product.
How much time?
Not long. just a few days.
I'll let you know when we're
ready for... for pickup.
That it?
Uh. no. listen.
Uh. prices are rising.
So. for the foreseeable future.
- we're gonna be dealing at 15 a key.
- 15?
50% hike. just like that?
Yeah.
You watch the news?
- Read the newspaper?
- Yeah.
Right. so then you know that the DEA
is on a rampage down in Colombia.
Yeah. I know that. but I just
kind of thought you
was immune to that shit.
What?
You know. thought...
thought you was immune.
You thought that I was immune to what.
supply and demand. or... ?
Never mind. 15's fine. hmm?
Yeah. no. no. I know it's fine.
I just... I'm just curious...
why it is you think that I'm not subject
to the basic laws of economics.
Hey. Franklin?
I don't know what it
is you think you know.
but I urge you to remember
that I am the only reason
that you are breathing
free air right now.
I'll put you back in that
cell any goddamn time I want.
Someone will be in
touch about the shipment.
Mm. you forgot to sign this page.
Did I? Sure.
And you forgot to sign this page.
Sorry.
Okay. What?
- Nothing.
- Mm-mm. That's not gonna fly.
What was our deal?
You ask. and I tell you.
- The truth.
- So. what is it?
Something about that shooting
in the projects the other night?
- Nah.
- Then what is it?
It's Reed Thompson.
What about him?
Well... I may have overstepped.
- Said something I shouldn't have.
- Like what?
- Franklin. you said he needed you.
- I know. I know.
That you had to be in this.
but as long as you're
pushing his-his product.
- he would protect you.
- And I still believe that.
So. what's the problem?
Mm.
I've had some terrible days in my life.
But nothing worse than
when I saw your face
behind that glass.
I'm in with you on this. from now on.
You said you had it under control.
And I'm happy to do
everything I can to help.
But it's up to you to protect everyone.
Can you do it or not?
Of course.
_
Hey. Pops.
Pops?
Hey. Welcome home. boy.
How's the ticker?
Uh...
she's still ticking.
Yeah. I-I went ahead and-and.
uh. briefed Dr. Wills.
You have an appointment Friday morning
- at 1000.
- Mm-hmm.
Get this thing a second look.
Yes. sir.
Theodore.
Sir.
You're looking well.
As are you.
You hungry?
I'm just tired.
Yeah. I-I made up the
spare. so. uh... in the back.
I-I wasn't sure if
you'd both be staying.
I-I just figured I'd stay on the couch.
- If that's all right.
- That's fine.
Yeah. Come on. let's-let's. uh...
It's good to see you.
Yeah.
Let me get that. I got it.
I got it.
Cookhouse on Avalon and
Manboy's crib on Rosecrans.
Now. they got dealers
working the Pueblos...
Cut the head off. the body will fall.
How many folks you need?
Four for each house. We
got to talk artillery.
I mean. the pistols will get it done...
... but we want to get our
hands on something heavy.
Sorry to interrupt. but. uh...
Manboy here to see y'all.
Manboy? You sure?
Well. I ain't ever met the
nigga. but that's what he say.
- He alone?
- Look that way.
Is he strapped?
Hey. Make sure he
clean. then send him in.
Fatback.
Keep a lookout.
Make sure it ain't a setup. Peach.
Okay.
Leon.
Y'all don't play with
that security. huh?
Feel like I should tip them
niggas. pat-down I just got.
'Sup. Lee? 'Sup. Saint?
- 'Sup. Drew?
- It's been a minute.
Been more than that.
You must be Jammin' Jerome.
Niggas out in Compton
talk about your shit.
Woofers blowing panties clean off.
My bad. I didn't know there
was a female in the house.
How you doing? My name is Drew.
Everybody call me Manboy.
- I'm Louie.
- Oowie.
Louie. How you end up with these...
- these undesirables?
- Hey. little boy.
The fuck you want here?
Guess you with him. huh?
I mean. I'll cut
straight to it if y'all...
I think that'd be best.
I'm a businessman.
Being as such. I'd say
it'd be in my interest
to know what the competition up to.
Unfortunately. a couple of my associates
took that notion a little too far.
You mean. tried to rob us?
That is indeed what I mean.
But I thought. seeing
as though how y'all ain't
out your rock or your cash.
and two of mine are already cooling.
you'll give me a chance to square us.
How you gonna do that?
First. I get my product from y'all.
Y'all shit cheaper and purer
than anything we're cooking up anyway.
That's it? That's your shit?
And I give you the nigga
that got away in the projects.
Say what?
The driver.
I'll tell you where he hiding out at.
Could do with him as you will.
That's my offer.
What y'all think?
I think.
24 hours. either your boy'll be dead
and we'd be in business.
or you...
and everybody you know will be gone.
And we won't.
Either way. you'll know soon.
You want the address
where my boy holing up at?
- Just in case?
- Nah.
We already got it.
Thank y'all for y'all time.
I'm-a show myself out.
Bye. Leon.
Our boys. they grew up. man.
- Good to see you.
- Just get the fuck out.
All right.
- Morning.
You want coffee?
I had mine hours ago.
How're the tomatoes doing this year?
Goddamn deer keep getting in 'em.
I should shoot 'em.
No... I wouldn't shoot
the tomatoes. sir.
God forbid someone discharge a firearm
in their own backyard.
I'm gonna get some coffee.
What happened to your brother?
I told you he's... there's damage
to the lining of his aorta.
West Point. flight school. Vietnam.
Strong as an ox. that boy.
He ran through walls his entire life.
What was that thing you used to say?
"Ships and harbor are safe.
but that ain't what ships are for."
Yeah. but some captains
bring their crews home intact.
So. what now?
A few more days. and you run off?
Back to the land of the
fruits and nuts and...
leave me to take care of him?
I have money.
I'll hire help for both of you.
Oh. that'll solve it.
I have work to do.
What's that?
Shuffling papers for
the State Department?
What is so important
that you can't clean up
your own goddamn mess?
Certainly isn't looking
after your own family.
I'll keep sending the money.
Yeah. keep your guilt
money. We don't want it.
Take care of yourself.
Motherfucker!
Met with our LAPD friend today.
It was Claudia. that shit at Jerome's.
He sure?
Yeah. he's still on her payroll. too.
I guess she tried to
get him to go at us.
and when he refused.
she found somebody else.
And I guess you ain't told Jerome yet.
You crazy? Hell no.
Shit. he'd fucking be shooting
that club up as we speak.
No. he think it's kids.
I'm gonna let him think it.
Yeah. Well. we got a lot on our plate
without worrying about fucking Claudia.
Yeah. I mean...
I'll try and talk some
sense to her before we act.
Okay.
Love you.
Hey. Chiquita.
- _
- I'm dying of thirst over here.
If only that were true.
How come you're always ignoring me?
Because you don't tip. pendejo.
You want a tip?
Just got to ask.
You motherfucker!
Ah. come on. mijita.
That's right. son.
That's enough.
Time to go.
Vamonos.
Fuck.
Ugh. You're the worst
bouncer we've ever had.
You should go to the hospital.
No.
No más hospitals.
Then you're coming home with me.
At least there I can patch you up right.
I'll be fine.
Hey.
You know she's not coming back. right?
We're closed.
Even old friends?
Hi. Gustavo.
Got a minute?
I lost Matt.
Means I'm down a pilot.
and I have product that I
need to get across the border.
And I was hoping to use
Lucia's family's farm
and their routes.
Lucia's gone.
She left months ago.
No idea where.
You want her family routes?
First. go find her.
I tried.
Only person there's
any record of is you.
You get a lot of parking tickets.
Look. Lucia must have talked
about the place at some point.
Where it is. who's still there.
She hated it.
She didn't talk to her mother.
I don't see what that
has to do with you.
Or business. I mean. if
they still have the farm.
they still have the trucks.
they still have the routes.
What do you want me to do?
Hmm? Just show up and
say. "Hi. I'm Gustavo.
I want to start a cocaine
business with you"?
You'd be amazed at how often that works.
Or stay here. keep getting
the shit kicked out of you
by drunk barflies.
It doesn't matter to me.
I'll find someone else.
Can I ask you one more question?
If Lucia's been gone for
months. why are you still here?
Just 'cause...
if it was me
and I was trying to find my girl.
I think that getting into
business with her family
would be a pretty good place to start.
It's Louie.
Pat her down.
She's good.
I have some things to say.
Didn't think they could wait.
Well. you better hurry
up. The tub's filling.
I came to apologize. Claudia.
for my part in what went down.
I never meant for it to go that way.
But you hurt me.
I hurt you?
I know you're upset.
but I'm here to tell you to let it go.
Let the past be the past.
You ever have a migraine?
The pain is crippling.
I've been to more doctors
than the Elephant Man.
I took all the pills.
And when that didn't work...
... I took matters into my own hands.
Care to join me?
Be a dear.
See you in the morning. Love you.
Evening. Franklin.
Been spending a lot of
time at your mama's house
since you been out.
Sure hope you don't have
her wrapped up in all this.
I got someplace I got to be. Andre.
Afraid that's gonna have to wait. son.
I'm gonna need you to
take a ride with me.
This official?
Nah.
It's just two neighbors talking.
So. you're not gonna
tell me where we going?
Let me ask you something.
What you see when you look at me?
Huh?
Certainly not the man
who you grew up with.
Who helped raise you after
your daddy disappeared
into that bottle.
So. what is it?
Gun and a badge. overprotective father
- or fucking asshole?
- You really want to know?
- I really do.
- I see a fraud.
A man who betrayed his people
to a system built to keep 'em down.
Is that what you think?
That I'm one of them?
If the combat boot fits.
Oh. damn.
I mean. did it ever occur
to you that I was a spy?
Doing time behind enemy lines.
- Trying to protect my people from that system.
- Oh. yeah?
And how's that working out for you?
I don't know. pusher man.
How's shit on your side of the line?
I see. I'm just some
nickel-and-dime thug. huh?
In this for the cars and pussy. right?
If the gold chain fits.
Ain't no rope around my neck. Andre.
Not like you.
And Joe Kennedy. he was
nothing but Mick trash...
till he wasn't.
And what'd he do?
Lifted his family up. and his boys...
they ran this country.
Now. that's real power.
Not a policeman's salary.
Taking orders from whitey.
You really want to help your people?
Best thing you could
do is toss that badge
back to the racist motherfuckers
that gave it to you.
and get on my side.
Unfortunately. Franklin.
that's not gonna work for me.
Don't knock it till you tried it.
That's just it.
I already did.
Bullshit.
Been back from 'Nam a few years.
I was working at the
Chrysler plant in Commerce.
When it closed. my wife up and left.
Baby girl to feed. mortgage to pay.
'Nam was a clusterfuck.
But Uncle Sam taught me a few things.
How to secure a location using force.
take what I wanted and get out.
What the fuck you saying?
Huh? You was a jacker? A bank robber?
What I'm saying is.
you take something
from a man at gunpoint.
you gonna feel a way about it.
At least I did.
Now. my bills were paid.
but I couldn't sleep.
Got tired of imagining the
cops busting in my door.
I still don't sleep
that good these days.
but at least it ain't my
conscience keeping me up.
Now. this rock that you're selling.
it's got a special hold.
It ain't weed or Sherm.
It's doing real damage out there.
And I think you know it.
So my question to you is...
How you sleeping at night. son?
Like a baby.
Well. now. you and me...
we at war.
Your business has gotten too big.
and now you exposed.
Your people out there right now
doing dirt on your behalf.
Oh. shit.
Making mistakes.
Mistakes that I'm going to catch.
No matter how small.
And which I will use
to bring you all down
one by one.
From your friends to your auntie...
... to your mama.
And then. when there
ain't nobody left...
... I'm going to take you. too.
See you soon. Franklin.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-